(Claire:)What an ass.
(Raj:)Please take me back.
Our love was meant to be!
I'm gonna be all alone
on Valentine's Day.
(Leonard:)Well, you were
right... tears.
(Amy:)Okay, and we are live
in 22 minutes.
(Sheldon:)I'm nervous.
I hope people
(Sheldon:)will be around to watch even
though it's Valentine's Day.
(Amy:)People who are fans
of an Internet show about flags?
(Amy:)Trust me, they're around.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and speaking
of Valentine's Day, I haven't
(Sheldon:)forgotten about you tonight.
(Amy:)What do you mean?
(Sheldon:)Well, you've become
such an integral
(Sheldon:)part of my life
as well as this show,
(Sheldon:)I felt it only right to include
your name in the title.
(Raj:)Oh.
(Amy:)That is so sweet.
(Sheldon:)So from now on, this program
will be officially known as
Dr. Sheldon Cooper
and Dr. Amy
Farrah Fowler
present Dr. Sheldon' Cooper's
Fun With Flags.